♪The night wind shakes off
the withered leaves♪
♪I open the window and gaze at the moon♪
♪Haze spreads across the river,
lanterns drifting♪
♪I hear the memories rustling♪
♪Garden flowers shed petals one by one♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
swaying with melancholy♪
♪I sigh by the lamp over the long night♪
♪Past memories unfold scene by scene♪
♪It's all your face♪
♪Boldly trampling over my heart♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for love miswritten♪
♪And another for youth passed♪
♪With endless sorrow,
I once traced your silhouette♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for joy and sorrow♪
♪And another for parting and reunion♪
♪I write until splendor fades,
and I am no more♪
=Prelude of the White Snake=
=Episode 19=
Then why not marry me first?
I can help you get your revenge.
How about that?
No.
I can't hold you back.
I've found a lead on my enemy.
I'll avenge them soon.
Wishful thinking.
You can never pull off
the revenge alone.
I never thought you'd doubt me.
Suzhen's snake spirit didn't react.
She really isn't Suzhen.
I never expected that demon
could conceal her aura so well.
Even Qing didn't notice.
That means she's very powerful.
I wonder how Miss Bai's been tortured.
You worry about her?
I just want to uncover
the truth quickly.
How about I go beat her up
until she tells us where Suzhen is?
Don't be rash.
She could even hurt Suzhen.
You're probably no match for her either.
What else can we do?
Well, Jinshan Temple
has a kind of powder.
I have an idea.
What powder?
We can put the powder in the flatbreads
and have her eat it.
Looking in the mirror again, Suzhen?
Apologize.
Aunt made some flatbreads.
Try one.
Apologize.
It was my fault earlier today.
I'm sorry.
That's right. Aunt and I
gave him a good scolding.
Aunt was right.
We should set our wedding date
as soon as possible.
Did Aunt really say that?
Aunt is the best.
Try the flatbreads.
They're delicious.
Aunt made these herself?
Anything Aunt makes is delicious.
Is it good?
Yes.
You have some too.
- We already ate.
- We had some.
What did you put in the flatbreads?
Tell me, where is Suzhen?
Where did you hide Suzhen?
I didn't expect
you'd find out after all.
If you're so capable,
find her yourselves!
Don't you dare run away!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Don't interfere.
Saving Suzhen comes first.
You know where she is?
Qing!
Are you alright?
The seal was just reinforced.
It's hard to break.
What about another way?
I can't think of any other way.
Forcing the Du'e Ancient Scroll
to work for you
will turn back on you harder.
I can't worry about that now.
We've exposed
the black snake's true form.
I must hurry and rescue Suzhen
before she recovers.
Have you lost your mind, Xu Xian?
You and Qing guard the entrance
so we don't get trapped inside.
I'll be right back.
Xu Xian!
Be careful.
My lord, I have failed the mission.
The mural world
was sealed by Jinshan Temple.
T-They even severely injured me as well.
Useless!
You can't even do that right.
What good are you?
But I managed to bring out
the remaining demonic energy
for you to use, my lord.
Good girl.
It wasn't in vain that I nurtured you
with my breath for years.
Remember this.
As long as you help me
escape this Jinshan array soon,
I won't mistreat you.
Had you not helped me be reborn
and raised me for years,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
I will go through fire and water for you
without hesitation.
Come, I'll heal your wounds.
Suzhen!
Xu Xian.
You're hurt. Don't move.
Let me help you up.
I'm sorry. I lied to you.
Don't speak.
Let me get you out first.
Suzhen, you're awake.
Don't move.
You're injured.
You're finally awake.
If you hadn't woken up,
he would've emptied Jinshan Temple's
entire medicine stash.
Suzhen, what on earth happened
inside the mural?
Actually,
the one who took me that day
wasn't Changming.
Who would've thought
that even inside the mural world,
you'd still have
such abundant spiritual power?
Who exactly are you?
Why did you take my form?
What do you mean, "take your form"?
I have been you all along.
What do you mean?
Have you forgotten?
Since you've forgotten,
let me help you remember.
Come on, become a part of me.
The mural world kept absorbing
my spiritual power,
so I couldn't defeat her
and was imprisoned in the dungeon.
But
during our fight,
I regained my lost memories.
Suzhen, you remember everything?
Was it you
who killed my parents back then?
♪I also gave my youth to someone♪
♪I must admit, you made the journey♪
♪When loving you
became instinct, what's left♪
♪Seals a fate too brutal to amend♪
♪Clumsy and new, we gave our first kiss♪
♪Never thought passionate eyes
would turn cold♪
♪I thought of pulling away,
but I'd barely begun♪
♪Having loved you so deep,
how could I love another♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I'm stubborn,
I never stopped you from loving others♪
♪I shouldn't have been so foolish
to think there was still hope♪
♪But you won't even admit what we had♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I have questions,
I never questioned you♪
♪I'll lock you away and set myself free♪
♪After all, I'm the one you deny♪
♪Having ever loved♪